Ray Hackshaw
33 Tui Street Point Chevalier
Auckland, New Zealand
+6421-023-2817
ray@rayhackshaw.com
rayhackshaw.com (wip)

Skills

Experience with Windows 7/8/10 OS, Linux distributions and macOS.

Intermediate understanding of Python 3.0, Java and C/C#.

Experience with web design, including HTML and CSS elements, as well as JavaScript, JSON and XML.

Experience in UX and User Experience design, with an understanding of the ideas of Don Norman, John Maeda and Jakob Nielsen. Experience using Sony Vegas Pro 12-15, Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Creative Suite. English fluency, conversational Japanese. Excellent communication skills, with a willingness to adapt and learn under pressure.

Work Experience

Saint Peter's College, Community service programme (2010 - 2016):

Volunteer community service initiative for students, with a focus on assisting those outside of your immediate/extended family who were less privileged/less fortunate than you.

Fairfax Media, Auckland Central (February 2015 - August 2016):

Paper runner distributing newspapers and advertisements within Point Chevalier, Auckland

Sky City, Auckland CBD (June - September 2015): waiter and Front of House staff member for catering functions at the Sky City Conventions Centre.

Albert's Post Bar & Eatery, Mount Albert (September 2017 - February 2019): Waiter and Front of House staff member. Main responsibilities included serving patrons, operating POS machines and arranging bookings.

Education

Highschool Certificate (IGCSE and CIE) Saint Peter's College, Epsom, Auckland 2010 - 2016

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science (Major) The University of Auckland, City Campus 2017 - current

Referees

Mr. Brad Bridges
Head of Faculty
Information and Communications Technology
Saint Peter's College, Epsom, Auckland
bbridges@st-peters.school.nz
+6427-599-9845

Steve and Anna Gough Business Owners Albert's Post Bar & Eatery, Mount Albert, Auckland hello@albertspost.co.nz

+6421-241-8645 (Steve) +6421-262-9561 (Anna)

Sam Madden-Hart Software Developer Hemisphere (www.hmsnz.com) sammaddenhart@gmail.com +6421-074-4874

Dr Rumi Sakamoto
Professor/Senior Lecturer of Japanese Studies
The University of Auckland, City Campus,
Auckland
r.sakamoto@auckland.ac.nz